<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Analysis on Owen&#39;s Math Portal</title>
    <link>https://drummond.nyc/tags/analysis/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Analysis on Owen&#39;s Math Portal</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://drummond.nyc/tags/analysis/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>A Collection of Exercises in Minimal Surfaces</title>
      <link>https://drummond.nyc/post/ms_exercises/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://drummond.nyc/post/ms_exercises/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;These are a collection of exercises in minimal surfaces, most of which are taken from &amp;ldquo;A Course in Minimal Surfaces&amp;rdquo; by Colding and Minicozzi. I am still adding to this document, so please feel free to contact me if you find any errors.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Monotonicity Formula for Energy Minimizing Maps and Monotone Quantities</title>
      <link>https://drummond.nyc/post/monotonicity_emm/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://drummond.nyc/post/monotonicity_emm/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Detailed proof of the monotonicity formula for energy minimizing maps and a discussion of the density function and monotone quanities.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Curvature, Stability, and Scalar Rigidity in Minimal Surface Theory</title>
      <link>https://drummond.nyc/post/grad-talk/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://drummond.nyc/post/grad-talk/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is the outline for a talk delivered on Feburary 21st, 2025 at the Rutgers student operated Grad Analysis Seminar.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hardy Spaces are Banach Spaces</title>
      <link>https://drummond.nyc/post/hardy-spaces/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://drummond.nyc/post/hardy-spaces/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The following is a short presentation on Hardy Spaces for MATH507 - Functional Analysis with Professor Maxime Van de Moortel. The presentation includes a brief introduction to H^p spaces and a proof that H^p is a Banach space for all p from 1 to infinity.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Collection of Exercises from Real Analysis II</title>
      <link>https://drummond.nyc/post/real-analysis-ex/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://drummond.nyc/post/real-analysis-ex/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The following exercises are an assortment of homework problems from &lt;em&gt;MATH 502 - Theory&#xA;of Functions of a Real Variable II&lt;/em&gt; with Professor Dennis Kriventsov at Rutgers University.&#xA;Topics include Radon Measures, weak convergence, Haar measures, Fourier analysis, PDEs,&#xA;distributions, and probability theory.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
