<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Analysis on Owen&#39;s Math Portal</title>
    <link>https://drummond.nyc/tags/analysis/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Analysis on Owen&#39;s Math Portal</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://drummond.nyc/tags/analysis/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Notes on Sobolev Spaces</title>
      <link>https://drummond.nyc/post/sobolevspaces/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://drummond.nyc/post/sobolevspaces/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;These are notes that I have compiled during my self-study for Sobolev Spaces. At the end, I have included several exercises, largely taken from Partial Differential Equations by Lawrence Evans. I am sure there may be errors in here, in which case feel free to email me.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Monotonicity Formula for Energy Minimizing Maps and Monotone Quantities</title>
      <link>https://drummond.nyc/post/monotonicity_emm/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://drummond.nyc/post/monotonicity_emm/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is an outline for the Rutgers Grad Analysis seminar talk that I delivered on 4/25/2025.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Abstract: In this talk, we will define energy minimizing maps and introduce key examples. Then, we will derive the associated variational formulae. A central theme of the talk will be the monotonicity formula: we will explore its significance and highlight its appearance in related geometric contexts such as minimal surfaces, mean curvature flow, and Ricci flow. We will then prove the monotonicity formula for energy minimizing maps. Finally, we will define the density function, introduce tangent maps, and discuss the role of monotone quantities in the study of regularity and singularities.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Collection of Exercises in Minimal Surfaces</title>
      <link>https://drummond.nyc/post/ms_exercises/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://drummond.nyc/post/ms_exercises/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;These are a collection of exercises in minimal surfaces, most of which are taken from &amp;ldquo;A Course in Minimal Surfaces&amp;rdquo; by Colding and Minicozzi. I am still adding to this document, so please feel free to contact me if you find any errors.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Curvature, Stability, and Scalar Rigidity in Minimal Surface Theory</title>
      <link>https://drummond.nyc/post/grad-talk/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://drummond.nyc/post/grad-talk/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is the outline for a talk delivered on Feburary 21st, 2025 at the Rutgers student operated Grad Analysis Seminar.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hardy Spaces are Banach Spaces</title>
      <link>https://drummond.nyc/post/hardy-spaces/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://drummond.nyc/post/hardy-spaces/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The following is a short presentation on Hardy Spaces for MATH507 - Functional Analysis with Professor Maxime Van de Moortel. The presentation includes a brief introduction to H^p spaces and a proof that H^p is a Banach space for all p from 1 to infinity.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Collection of Exercises from Real Analysis II</title>
      <link>https://drummond.nyc/post/real-analysis-ex/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://drummond.nyc/post/real-analysis-ex/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The following exercises are an assortment of homework problems from &lt;em&gt;MATH 502 - Theory&#xA;of Functions of a Real Variable II&lt;/em&gt; with Professor Dennis Kriventsov at Rutgers University.&#xA;Topics include Radon Measures, weak convergence, Haar measures, Fourier analysis, PDEs,&#xA;distributions, and probability theory.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
